Choosing what to wear can be a tricky problem, especially if you’re a fashion victim.
选衣服有时候是个棘手的问题，尤其如果你是一个“时尚受害者”的话。
Trying to keep up with the latest styles involves regular visits to the shops and sometimes forking out for expensive designer clothes.
想要跟上最新潮流，就得经常逛商店，有时还得花大价钱买昂贵的设计师品牌服装。
But when the fashion changes, these clothes languish in the back of cupboards gathering dust, or just get thrown away.
但当潮流改变时，这些衣服就会被闲置在衣柜深处积灰，或者干脆被扔掉。
There are many stores that now offer cheap ‘fast fashion’ – low-price items that imitate the styles of more expensive designer brands.
现在有很多商店都在售卖廉价的“快时尚”产品——这些低价商品模仿高价设计师品牌的款式。
Environmentalists are angered by the amount of energy involved in making these clothes and that many of them are made from non-recyclable materials.
环保人士对生产这些衣服所耗费的大量能源感到愤怒，而且其中许多衣服是由不可回收材料制成的。
This means that items are just incinerated or go into landfill.
这意味着这些衣物最终只会被焚烧或送进垃圾填埋场。
Writing about this for the BBC, Eleanor Lawrie says that people in the UK are the worst in Europe for doing this - with a million tonnes of unwanted textiles a year being discarded.
埃莉诺·劳里在为英国广播公司撰写相关文章时表示，英国人在这方面是欧洲最糟糕的——每年有100万吨废弃纺织品被丢弃。
And she says “on top of often poor labour conditions for garment workers, the fashion industry is responsible for 20% of the world's waste water, and 10% of carbon emissions.”
她还说：“除了服装工人往往面临恶劣的劳动条件外，时尚产业还造成了全球20%的废水排放和10%的碳排放。”
This is something the fashion industry is becoming more aware of and has led to a new crop of biomaterials that replace wasteful textiles like cotton and leather.
时尚产业逐渐意识到这一问题，这也催生了一批新型生物材料，以替代棉花和皮革等耗资源的纺织品。
Examples include Piñatex, a leather-like substance made from discarded pineapple leaves. It's been used in collections by Hugo Boss and H&M.
例如，Piñatex（菠萝皮皮革）是一种由废弃菠萝叶制成的类皮革材料，已被雨果博斯（Hugo Boss）和H&M用于服装系列中。
And there’s mycelium, the root structure of mushrooms, that’s being used to create food, packaging and textiles.
还有菌丝体（蘑菇的根系结构），目前正被用于生产食品、包装和纺织品。
Cotton is a very resource-intense crop to grow.
棉花是一种种植过程消耗资源极高的作物。
Eleanor Lawrie says “about 15,000 litres of water [are] required to make one pair of jeans.”
埃莉诺·劳里说：“制作一条牛仔裤大约需要15000升水。”
So, buying organic cotton is a better choice.
因此，购买有机棉是更好的选择。
And there is also Tencel, also known as Lyocell, a natural product that's now growing in popularity.
此外还有天丝（Tencel，也称为莱赛尔纤维），这是一种天然产品，如今正越来越受欢迎。
It's made by extracting cellulose fibre from trees; its manufacture is thought to use 95% less water than cotton processing.
它通过从树木中提取纤维素纤维制成，其生产过程消耗的水量据信比棉花加工少95%。
But creating sustainable textiles is only part of the battle – buying ethically, buying second hand and buying fewer clothes are the obvious environmentally friendly choices.
但制造可持续纺织品只是这场战役的一部分——理性消费（关注环保及劳工权益）、购买二手衣物以及减少购衣数量，才是显而易见的环保选择。
Dr Richard Blackburn from Leeds School of Design told the BBC that “I don't think you should consider buying any item of clothing unless you commit to 30 wears.
利兹设计学院的理查德·布莱克本博士向英国广播公司表示：“我认为，除非你能保证一件衣服穿30次以上，否则就不应该考虑购买它。
Unless you can do that you're not even starting to be sustainable.”
如果做不到这一点，你就根本算不上开始践行可持续理念。”